Hello everyone! I'm Momoko Yamada of Nyally Call Joy and
This is Alice Yamada and Momo no Ko no!
Yes, so as some of you may be able to tell from the background
The three of us came to visit Sanrio Purond today!
Thank you!
Yes, I really love Sanrio Puronde.
We usually have a lot of Sanrio stuff with us.
I feel like we are the three Sanrio lovers in Joy.
So, we're going to have fun all day today!
I'm off!
First, I'm going to see the departure of the train!
I'm looking forward to it!
I always go for the Shillong Finish!
This is the one I've been after, and I'm going to match it with some clothes!
I'm going to go with this pattern and this one!
I'm going for this one! That was quick! I'm going straight for it.
What's everyone else's?
The black one is a new design.
Is this a Halloween version?
Halloween is so cute!
I think I'll do Halloween.
I'll go with this one then!
It's Halloween!
Yes, it is.
What's wrong, Alice?
Sure thing.
This?
It looks possible.
It's possible.
What about Alice? And Alice?
This limited edition.
I'll do the limited edition.
I'll go with this outfit.
It matches my outfit.
I'm going with the black one.
It's the Halloween version of the Kuromi.
I love Halloween.
Can I buy some of these?
Yay! I'm so happy!
Everyone has a different character.
It's already fun!
Yeah, this is probably the most fun part of the catsuit edibi...
Wait, there's a big conoisseur!
This one looks like him. Oh my gosh!
He looks like Conoa.
That's true! I wanted to find a character who looks like everyone else!
We can do that with characters!
So many things have evolved!
I like Batsumaru, too.
Batsumaru looks like Lennon.
He looks like Lennon.
Lennon is here.
It's really cute.
He's cute.
Wait, wait, wait.
I can't wait to meet the coach.
I can't wait to be with you.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I want to do it. I want to do it.
Want to do it?
Yes! I'll do it!
Don't you think Dorne is cute?
Dorne is cute too.
She's cute.
I'm definitely going to do the random ones.
Which one?
I don't know.
I'll choose this one.
It's decided.
Ta-da!
I just got it.
Shall I put on Captain Shang?
Yes, sir.
How do you like it?
I'm on key.
He's cute.
You're wearing a captain shan.
Yay!
Now that I've finally got it all dyed in, let's go put it on the presenter, Maru.
Let's go put it on the presenter, Mr. Maru.
What is this place?
The food counter.
It says "restaurant.
I love it.
This is where all the characters sit.
This is the Kitty Zone. This is Kitty's zone.
And over there is Mr. Mayonnaise.
and it says
It's so cute!
When Alice and I came here before
we went to the Kitty Zone.
That's nice.
This one.
Oh, my God.
Is it?
What is it?
I don't know.
I don't know about this.
Where do I put it?
Oh, yeah.
It's got a hood in it.
You like hoods, don't you?
Okay, then.
I'll take this one, too.
It'd be bad if everyone had one of these.
I'm totally okay with that one.
I think I'll have this one, too.
Really?
Then we should all do this.
I'll do this.
Let's eat.
I'm with you.
Dinner's ready.
All of you.
It's all the same.It's all the same.
This is YouTube-wise, that's what it is.
I mean, we're good friends.
My Melo's.
Roast beef.
I asked for it.
This is Miumo.
See?
So cute!
My Melo is here.
It's nice.
I'll have a melon soda.
Same here.
Let's eat.
Ready?
Bon appétit.
I like it.
Melon soda.
Tastes like it always does.
Want some? Here.
Try it.
My Melo, what will it taste like?
Bon appétit!
What is it?
It tastes like lefers!
Lefers?
Is it sweet?
Sweet?
Maybe it's sweet.Could be sweet.
Might be sweet.
Could be sweet.
Tastes like it always does.
It's got some kind of aojiso on it, so...
It's got green perilla on it.
It's got some aojiso on it.
Like aojiso flavor.
My Melo!
My Melo.
Is it good?
Delicious.
Tasty?
Yes, it is.
Now you're right.
Last time we did this, it was just the two of us.
We enjoyed it a lot, didn't we?
So fast.
We did the whole thing already.
Everything was going to be faster.
And the name updates and stuff.
There was a huge line of people lined up to get their names updated and stuff.
That's good, right?
It was good.
It was fun.
Last time, I made Cinnamon.
I made Cinnamon and Alice made Kitty.
But today it's the other way around.
It's the other way around.It's the other way around.
So...
I just finished it!
Thank you for the food!
Delicious!
Okay, then.
Let's say hello.
Yes, ma'am.
Ready?
Thank you for the food.
Boo-hoo!
They're lining up.
What is this place?
This place is called... Pink Studio.
You remember this?
I didn't know that either.
Yeah, I thought it wasn't here when Sakuchi came.
Wow!
Well, let's do the uncount for the first time.
Ta-da!
Oh, it's in there.
Here it is.
Enter, enter.
I've got him calling Enter.
Here's the entrance.
Here.
The title.
Here it is.
Twinkling StudioTwin Cling Studio
Twin Cling
Have you ever heard the term "twinkling"?
Twinkling Studio
It's sparkling lame.
It's so sparkly.
What's the point of today's makeup?
Today, lame.
Seriously, it's kind of nice.
It's definitely a cover-up.
The cover-up is really different.
I thought it was unusual.
I finally did it
But, you know, Conan, too.
It's rare to see glittering lame.
It's really something.
I've been hooked on it since Jiri showed me how to do it.
That's great, Jiri!
She's the master of glitter.
He's a master of glitter.
I'm going to have to ask him to do something in front of me from now on.
I'm in.
Oh, my God.
You're so pretty.
Where's the mirror?
It's hard to tell what's wrong with it.
You're in the mirror.
Oh, my God. Oh, man.
This is a maze.
It's a maze!
This is the next company.
There are a lot of places to take pictures.
There are a lot of photo spots.
Yes, it's a maze.
Which one is the maze?
I know which one is the maze.
Oh, no.
Oh, shit.
Which one are you doing?
This guy, he's so nippy.
Both of you.
Wait a minute.
This is comical.
Nice work.
If you ever get an acting job...
I'd look good in it.
I'd be good in it.
That kind of role.
I'd be smiling.
But...
I like it.
Cute.
It's hard.
This is playful.
I like the switch from nippy to nippy.
You should try it, Alice.
I can do it.I can do it.
Right now?
Are you working on it?
I'm panicking.
Where are you?
I'm just keeping a straight face.
It's hard.
Great. Let's do it together.
Practice.
I've made it so we can all do it.
Might as well use it.
I'm going to see Kitty now.
I'm looking forward to it
It's your wish, isn't it?
I'll leave it to you.
I've made it to Kitty's specifications today.
I'm going to meet the real Kitty.
Here it is.
Kitty's here.
Kitty's only here, right?
See you later, see you later, bye-bye.
See you next time.
Kitty, you're in.
Kitty's account.
Thank you.
Bye-bye.
Good night.
I'm hungry.
Oh, God, I'm so hungry.Oh, God, I'm so hungry.
Oh my God, I'm starving.
I think I'm gonna get something to eat, have a drink, relax a little bit.
What are you having? Lemonade?
Something that changes color. Is it a Halloween special?
I ordered the Mont Blanc.
The top one is Kitty.
I ordered a yogurt drink.
The Wish Me Myrtle one.
I'd like to order this one.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm ordering.
Bon appétit!
Delicious!
Delicious
Lemonade
It tastes like lemonade.
It's a strong Mont Blanc!
It is a Mont Blanc pasta, so
self-proclaimed
Yes, it is.
It tastes like blueberries.
Delicious.
Cute desk.
Do you have a 20?
Hey, guys. Hey, guys.
It's the 20th anniversary.
We'll adjust to it.
They're more alive than we are.
Cinnamon.
I'm like you, and I'd like to say something.
classmate
Camera.
We have to be careful with Cinnamon.
An-chan says it's cheap.
An-chan is good.
Boo boo... today we had a full day of visiting Anchan Reappearance, visiting all of the places we have visited, and eating lots of delicious food... it was a great day!
It was Aloin's day, so I had a lot of fun.
Let's boo boo!
It's okay, do it again!
If you like this video, please rate it highly, subscribe to the channel, and leave a comment!
That's all for now, this is Nyari and Obucho!
Bye bye!
ED
Subtitles & Subtitles by Kyou